Guide to the Alumni Affairs Education and Travel Records, 1987-2008 UA.14.01.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Alumni Affairs Education and Travel Records
1987-2008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Office of Alumni Affairs
UA.14.01.0002
7.0 Linear Feet
Education and travel records from the Alumni Affairs Office including fliers, correspondence, and memoranda.
Access Restrictions
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use of administrative records. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Provenance
Transfer, 2011, 2019.
Collection Overview
Education and travel records from the Alumni Affairs Office including fliers, correspondence, and memoranda.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is unprocessed and may require arrangement and/or rehousing before use. Materials have not been screened for sensitive or restricted content. Staff will need to screen materials before use. Please contact Research Services for more information.
Conditions Governing Access
This list of contents was provided by the donor and has not been verified by University Archives staff.
Biographical / Historical
The Duke Alumni Association's travel program arranges trips for alumni and a Duke faculty host to a wide variety of locations. Trips and destinations have included a South American Amazon cruise, a cruise through the Panama Canal, Morocco, Greece, Italy, Spain, England, and others.
Voyages and travels; Duke University. Office of Alumni Affairs; Duke University -- Alumni and alumnae
- Unprocessed materials
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 1-5)
- Accession UA2019.0049, 1999-2008
  Scope and Contents
  Each item listed in this series is a photo album.
  - Duke Alumni Trip with Professor Joel Colton [France], April 1999 (Box 6)
  - Multiple Trips, 1999-2000 (Box 6)
    Meeting of alumni travel coordinators in the west, sponsored by Stanford; Weekend with alumni and Dean Willimon at The Swag in the NC mountains, 1999; Quebec with fellow university travel coordinators, 2000; Duke Alumni trip to Provence, April 2000
  - Village Life in Wales, July 31, 2000-August 8, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Oxford Experience, September 2000 (Box 6)
  - Treasures of the Seine, October 17, 2000-October 28-2000 (Box 6)
  - Trip to Russia on Viking ship, early 2000s (Box 6)
  - London Theater Week, 2001 (Box 6)
  - Lake District, July 2002 (Box 6)
  - Oxford Experience, 2004 (Box 6)
  - The Art and Architecture of Spain: Barcelona, Parador, Bilboa, San Sebastian, Madrid, April 22, 2004-May 4, 2004 (Box 6)
  - South American Cruise down the Amazon, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Yorkshire Trip and Oxford Program, 2005 (Box 7)
  - [Greece], 2006 (Box 7)
  - Crystal Cruise through Panama Canal, February 2006 (Box 7)
  - Oxford Experience, circa 2006 (Box 7)
  - Italian Lakes: Baveno, Italy, May 22, 2007-May 30, 2007 (Box 7)
  - China trip (Silk Road) with China Advocates and Kim Rorshach, Director for Nasher, 2007 (Box 7)
  - China trip souvenir album from Beijing with group photograph, 2007 (Box 7)
  - Moroccan Discovery, March 2008 (Box 7)